const questions: Array<NumbersQuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'רִאשׁוֹן',
    answers: ['eerste'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שֵׁנִי',
    answers: ['tweede'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שְׁלִישִׁי',
    answers: ['derde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'רְבִיעִי',
    answers: ['vierde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֲמִישִׁי',
    answers: ['vijfde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שִׁשִּׁי',
    answers: ['zesde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שְׁבִיעִי',
    answers: ['zevende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'שְׁמִינִי',
    answers: ['achtste'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'תְּשִׁיעִי',
    answers: ['negende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עֲשִׂירִי',
    answers: ['tiende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson12OrdinalNumbers: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson12-ordinal-numbers',
  name: 'Les 12 – Rangtelwoorden (m)',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson12OrdinalNumbers
